# Nodir Navruzov



spy.nowin@gmail.com



+998999969538



in linkedin.com/in/nodir-navruzov

https://github.com/nodirnavruzov

# **Summary**

I'm backend developer with experience in JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, MongoDB, HTTP, WebSocket, Vue.js, Nuxt.js and more. I write code to a server, develop user interface, set up integration between the client and server sides, connect the project to database, create REST API, find and fix bugs

# **Experience**



### **Full-stack Developer**

ProDVD

Oct 2021 - Present (5 months +)

## **Javascript Developer**

ProDVD

Sep 2020 - Oct 2021 (1 year 2 months)

# **Education**



### Tax college, Tashkent

Tax specialist Sep 2012 - Jun 2016

### **Skills**

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Express.js
- WebSocket
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- ORM
- Rest API
- Model-View-Controller (MVC)
- Nuxt.js
- Vue.js